http://www.jeffersonhospital.org/patients-and-visitors/patient-policies/online-privacy-statement/

1-800-JEFF-NOW
Breadcrumb trail:
Patient Policies
Advance DirectivesAdvance Directives (Spanish)Financial AssistanceEthics CommitteePatient RightsCivil Rights CompliancePrivacy PracticesPrivacy Practices (Chinese)Privacy Practices (Spanish)Safe HavenWebsite Terms of UseWebsite Privacy Statement
Online Privacy Statement
Thomas Jefferson University Hospitals has created this statement to demonstrate our commitment to on-line privacy. It discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
You may visit our website without submitting any information about yourself. If you send us e-mail or subscribe to one of our on-line publications, you will be asked to submit information about yourself. We will use this information for replying to your message or forwarding the requested material. We do not share this information with any other partners, affiliates or members of JHS. Our website may log the IP addresses of visitors, but only to administer the site and diagnose problems with our server. IP addresses are not used to identify individuals.
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy practices or content.
Please note that TJUH will not respond to any question concerning a specific medical or health condition. If you submit such a request you will receive a standard response that you should consult with your own health care professional. Of course, we will not intentionally share the contents of this type of an e-mail with any third party. However, due to the nature of electronic communications, we cannot and do not provide any assurances that the contents of your e-mail will not become known or accessible to third parties. WE URGE YOU NOT TO PROVIDE ANY CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU OR YOUR HEALTH TO US VIA ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATION. If you do so, it is at your own risk.
Google AdWords and Analytics
Thomas Jefferson Univeristy Hospitals utilizes Google Analytics on its web properties to track the effectiveness and relevance of our web site to visitors. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of hospitals.jefferson.edu, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
Information about data collected by Google can be found by visiting http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
Questions or Comments?
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, you can contact us.
Also, please read the terms of use for this Web site.
×
Call 1-800-JEFF-NOW
Close
